

JULIAN RAZIF FIGARO

Full-stack Java and JavaScript Developer

SUMMARY

Proven experience developing customer-focused websites using full stack Java and JavaScript. Build products for web, and mobile app users over 3+ years. meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations, and databases.

PROFESSIONAL SKILS

CODING LANGUAGES

Java, and JavaScript.

TECH STACKS

React, React Native, Vue, NodeJS, Express, Sequelize, GraphQL, Apollo Server, Socket.io, Java Spring Boot, Kafka, Redis, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Intellij, Maven, ServerSentEvent, WebSocket, Git, Jenkins, Docker, Helm, Kubernetes, Rancher, MVC, Stream, SPA, RestAPI, Microservices, DevOps.

HOW TO REACH ME

Cell:

+62 858-8261-3820

Address:

Cakung, East jakarta

Linkedin:

/in/julianrazif

GitHub:

<u>julianrazif</u>

Email:

julian.razif@gmail.com

EDUCATION

HACKTIV8 INDONESIA AUG 2020 TO NOV 2020

Immersive full stack JavaScript

- Enrolled since Aug. 2020 to Nov. 2020.
- Learn full-stack JavaScript web development.

POLITEKNIK UNIVERSITAS ANDALAS (PNP)

2007 - 2011

Diploma, Computer Engineering GPA - 3.05

Accredited B.

PROJECTS

COMPANY PROJECT DEC 2020, SEP 2021

 Stack: React, React Native, Java Spring Boot, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Kafka, Redis, ServerSentEvent, WebSocket, Git, Jenkins, Docker, Helm, Kubernetes, Rancher, AWS.

SUGOKU

NOV 2020

 $\frac{https://expo.io/@julianrazif/projects/julian-sugoku}{}$

- An intuitive mobile app to hone your logic and fill your spare time.
- Stack: React Native, redux, Expo.

C-BUDGET NOV 2020

https://expo.io/@julianrazif/projects/c-budget

- C-Budget is a mobile-friendly app solution for vision impaired friends to control their budget.
- Stack: React, React Native, Redux, Expo, Express & NodeJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, JWT, Jest, GCP (Vision API, Cloud Storage, Compute Engine).

CAREER SUMMARY

SENIOR DEVELOPER

DEC 2020 TO AUG 2022 PT. Trix Studio Games

· Developed the applications.

IT & SYSTEM DEVELOPER

FEB 2020 TO JUN 2020 PT. CKD Trading Indonesia

- Installed and configured the computer hardware, software, and systems.
- Designed the software and systems to help work more efficiently.
- Integrated the data from several systems and databases.
- Developed the JavaScript applications (Kintone).

IT SUPERVISOR

JUN 2019 TO DEC 2019 PT. Kaneka Foods Indonesia

- Successfully implemented ERP systems (MCFrame, ProPlus, MES).
- Successfully implemented IT infrastructure in the new factory.
- Realized excellent IT operations.